本字幕由 ShinY深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译｜J爱迷离　月壹　饭团
校对｜爽爷　　后期｜大囧蛙　小滔
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
功夫小蝇
Eage
爸爸… 爸爸…
Father... father...
爸爸！
Father!
给我讲个故事吧 爸爸
Tell me a story, father.
今天太晚了 宝贝儿 睡觉吧
lt's late night dear, go to sleep.
求你了 爸爸 就讲一个！
Please dad, just one story!
明天再给你讲
l'll tell you tomorrow.
爸爸 你昨天晚上也是这么说的
Dad, you promised the same thing last night too.
讲个嘛 爸爸… 爸爸…
Please tell. Father... father...
爸爸 讲个嘛！
Father, please tell me!
让爸爸睡觉！你也安静地睡觉
Allow dad to sleep! You too sleep silently.
爸爸… 爸爸…
Father... father...
求你了 爸爸…
please father...
看会动画片 宝贝儿
Watch cartoon channel, dear.
现在没有电视节目！
No TV now!
讲个故事快点睡觉
Tell a story and put to sleep.
讲一个 爸爸… 讲一个
Tell me father... tell me.
好吧…
Okay...
在很久很久以前 有一位国王…
Once upon a time in a place, there lived a King...
国王有七个儿子
The King had seven sons
他们出去狩猎 然后带回来七条大鱼
and they went to hunt and brought seven fishes,
这个故事已经讲过很多次了 爸爸！
it's very old story, father!
听都听烦了 爸爸
Got bored hearing it many a times, father.
给我讲个新故事吧 爸爸 给我讲个新故事吧
Tell me some new story. Father, tell me a new story.
别在我耳边像只小蜜蜂似的
Don't buzz like a bee
嗡嗡吵个不停…
in my ear...
等一下…
wait...
你想听个新故事 是吗？
You want a new story, right?
很久很久以前
Once upon a time in place,
有一只小苍蝇…
there lived a Fly...
苍蝇！？继续…
Fly!? Carry on...
和小苍蝇住在一起的还有一个坏人…
ln the same place along with the Fly there lived a bad boy...
坏人？他叫什么名字？
Bad boy? What's his name?
他的名字叫苏迪普！
Sudeep!
这边正开着董事会呢 而你却在这里…
Board meeting is going and you are here...
无聊的会议而已！
Bore meeting!
我已经竭尽全力了！
l tried a lot!
官员并没有按照我们的想法行事
Officer is not coming our way,
我用不用把他干掉？
shall l bump him off?
你为什么总是如此崇尚暴力呢？
Why are you so violent always?
这么说你倒是希望和平解决问题了
And you're an epitome of peace.
你每天都来这里吗？
Do you come here every day?
希望我每天都来吗？
Want me to come?
- 什么时间？ - 一切随你！
- What time?  - Your time!
有什么新的作品吗？
Doing anything new?
过来看看！
Take a look!
不错！那是什么？
Good! What's that?
真的吗？我还想在中间镶嵌一颗心！
What good? l'm trying to unite a heart in it!
但是不管怎样都不令我满意
But l'm not satisfied.
如果我和你哥哥能够团聚的话 你就会满意了
Better try to unite me with your brother, you'll get satisfaction.
我住在这里 而他却住在迪拜！
l'm here and he's in Dubai!
快睡觉吧 都晚上十点了！
Go to bed, it's 10 pm!
嫂子 只有几户人家停电了
Sister-in-law, power is shut only in few homes.
麻烦你给供电局打个电话
Please dial electricity office.
他们竟然给按时交电费的用户断电
They cut the power of those who pay bills on time.
你把这些都倒出来干什么？
Why are you pouring it out?
我在问你话呢 纳尼！
l'm asking you, Nani!
你在做什么？
What man?
你疯了吗？
Have you gone mad?
♫ 我是纳尼… 我是纳尼… ♫
♪ l'm Nani... l'm Nani... ♪
♫ 我是你永不离弃的影子… ♫
♪ l'm your never leaving shadow... ♪
这是什么？
What's this?
♫ 照亮我的双眸… ♫
♪ Lighting the wicks of my eyes... ♪
♫ 给我追梦的翅膀… ♫
♪ Giving wings to my dreams... ♪
♫ 让我在天空翱翔… ♫
♪ l'm floating in air... ♪
宾都 睡觉 都深夜了！
Bindu, go to bed, its late night!
好的 嫂子！
Okay, sister-in-law!
♫ 看见你 我已心满意足 ♫
♪ When seen, it's okay, ♪
♫ 即使消失 我也心甘情愿… ♫
♪ even fading away is okay... ♪
你怎么还能笑着面对这一切？
How can you still smile?
到现在为止 你已经为她痴迷整整两年了！
You've been after her madly for 2 years now!
她会在意你的关心么？
Did she care to look back at you?
你煞费苦心地为她照亮房间
You took trouble to light her room,
她连最起码的感谢都没有？
did she at least thank you?
她是因为爱我才拉上窗帘的
She drew the curtains down for the love she has for me.
- 是吗？ - 是的！
- What?  - Yes!
如果她不拉窗帘的话
lf she doesn't,
她就会知道我将站在这离彻夜不眠
she knows l'll keep awake all night here.
黑暗 迷雾 寒冷 她可不忍心看我病倒
Darkness, fog, chill, she can't bear to see me falling sick.
这就是原因 尽管她不希望如此
That's why, though she doesn't like it,
却还是情不自禁拉上窗帘
she closed it against her will.
我们名单上面的客户…
Our guest list...
他拒绝和我们签订合同
He refuses to sign our files
却还来参加我们的派对！
but attends our party!
绵薄之意 不成敬意！
A small gift from me!
感谢您为派对带来活力！
You've added life to this party!
顺便说一句
By the way
我的夫人卡拉也来了！
my wife Kala is here,too!
♫ 信不信由你 ♫
♪ Believe it or not ♪
♫ 世界因我的爱而疯狂… ♫
♪ the world is mad after my love... ♪
- 您好！ - 您好！
- Greetings!  - Greetings!
我的妻子酷爱射击！
My wife too loves shooting!
他可是个大忙人 老公！
He's a busy man, hubby!
♫ 我的名字是希拉… ♫
♪ My name is Sheela... ♪
♫ 希拉是一个妙龄女子… ♫
♪ Sheela's sensuous youth... ♪
跟我来！
Come with me!
我们一度绞尽脑汁想尽一切办法
We were breaking heads
希望能够搞定他…
how to bring him to our line...
你被他的老婆迷住了吗？
Did you charm his wife?
有哪个女人不会爱上你？
ls there any woman who will not fall for you?
倒是有一个！
There is one!
我的老婆！
My wife!
我对她一见钟情 到手之后却想甩了她
l fell for her at first sight and wanted to leave after having her.
但是后来我看上了她的财富！
But later on my eyes fell on her wealth!
于是我娶了她
l married her.
我让她交出财产 她说除非我死了！
l asked her to give the property. She said on my dead body!
还有一些学校需要我们捐赠学习材料 宾都
There are still schools where we've to supply study materials, Bindu.
旧城贫民窟希望学校需要捐赠
Delivered 50 Hindi books
五十本北印度课本
to Old City Slum Govt. School
巴朗热希望学校需要捐赠黑板
Black boards to Balanagar Govt. school,
有四到五个班的学生需要捐赠英语课本
English text books to four and five classes,
我们这周就得捐赠出去
we've to deliver it by this week.
他们很快就要考试了
Their exams too are approaching.
银行存款余额是多少？
What's the bank balance?
一万五千六百卢比！
Rs.15600!
阿嘎沃尔的善民们承诺支票捐款 是吗？
Agarwal Sweets people promised to pay cheque, right?
我们为了募集善款支出的费用
We're spending more to collect it
比他们捐赠的还要多得多！
than what they donate!
这就是我来这里的原因！
That's why l'm here!
像之前每月一样
Like every month,
我用辛苦赚来的钱来帮助你解决问题
to solve your problem with my hard earned money,
请为我的捐赠保守秘密 我不喜好张扬！
Please keep my donation a secret. l hate publicity!
什么？匿名捐赠？
What? Secret donation?
这就是我没有签支票的原因！
That's why l didn't even sign my cheque!
没有签名的支票是无法兑现的
Cheque without signature will be dishonoured!
作为捐款人 我想知道
As a donor l want to
我上个月捐款的使用情况
know how you spent the funds l donated last month,
能麻烦您告诉我吗？
will you please tell me?
你想要银行为你区区十五卢比的捐款
Do you want bank balance sheet
开具存款证明吗？
for your paltry Rs.15 donation?
真应该让她立刻闭上嘴巴！
Must cut her to size immediately!
比起披肩发 你把头发扎起来会更美
You'd look better if you tie your hair instead of letting it down.
我喜欢松散的感觉！
l love loose!
确实有点松散的感觉
Indeed you're loose,
不过至少把头发弄紧点！
at least keep your hair tight!
请您继续！
You continue please!
上个月 我们在课本 石板瓦片
We spent Rs.90000 on books, slates
和杂费方面花费了九万卢比
and fees last month.
如果您希望了解更详细的…
lf you want more details...
你的声音如珍珠般圆润…
Your words are pearls...
你十分迷人！
You're very beautiful!
洋溢着微笑…
Spill few smiles...
你不笑的时候也十分迷人！
You're beautiful even when you don't smile!
邦蒂今晚会回来！
Bunty is coming today evening!
尽管很生气 我希望你…
Though angry, l wish you...
嫂子 你怎么来了？
How come you're here, sister-in-law?
我来这儿有要紧的事要商量
l'm here to talk about an important matter.
苏迪普建筑公司预计会捐赠一大笔钱
Sudeep Constructions are intending to make huge donation.
去见见他们的总经理吧！
Meet their MD!
- 怎么能见到他呢？ - 这儿有他的名片
- How to meet him?  - Here's his visiting card.
我从我老板桌子上偷的
l stole it from my boss' table.
嫂子！
Sister-in-law!
你要是把他的信用卡也偷过来
Had you stolen his credit card,
我们就可以得到一大笔捐款了
we could've donated big money!
这家伙怎么来这儿捣乱了？
How come the fireworks are cracking here?
可不是你想的那样 你还是走吧
There's nothing like that, you can leave.
审计员表示如此大额流动资金
Auditor says it's not safe
保管起来并不安全
to keep large amount of liquid cash.
这是苏迪普的地盘！没人敢动那笔资金！
This is Sudeep's Kingdom! No man would dare touch it!
总经理 五一一项目工程办公室的人
Sir, someone is here for you
希望和您见面…
from Project 511 office...
安排股东大会
Arrange a meeting with investors.
总经理正在开一个重要会议…
Sir is in an important meeting...
请那个女孩进来
Send the girl in.
♫ 熔岩… 熔岩… ♫
♪ Lava... lava... ♪
♫ 心如熔岩般流动… ♫
♪ heart is flowing with lava... ♪
我是宾都 五一一项目工程的负责人…
l'm Bindu, coordinator of project 511...
♫ 你是月光中的喷发的熔岩吗？♫
♪ Are you an erupting volcano in moonlight? ♪
♫ 如气息间的盘旋不止的旋风… ♫
♪ Like a typhoon in breath... ♪
♫ 如臂弯中滚滚而来的卷风… ♫
♪ like a tornado in my arms... ♪
♫ 你会使我甘愿殉情吗？♫
♪ Will you come and kill me? ♪
先生 如果您慷慨解囊…
Sir, if you donate generously...
我曾做过慈善事业
l've made a donation,
我能成为你们的其中一员吗？
can l become a member?
我很欣赏你的善举
l like your intention.
我想进一步了解你！
l want to observe you closely!
简直难以置信 先生
l can't believe it, sir.
请您收下 先生
Please take it, sir.
迷你艺术品！我亲手制作的
Micro Art! l made it.
我该走了 先生
l'll take leave sir.
一百五十万卢比？你就这么喜欢她？
Rs.15 lakhs? Do you like her so much?
你看起来很高兴 宾都？
You seem to be very happy, Bindu?
神父 我们为工程筹到了一大笔捐款
Priest, we got a huge donation for our project.
- 为还此殊愿所捐  - 好的 亲爱的
- Offer special prayers.  - Okay dear.
快看 她因为我的捐钱而来到这里还愿
See, she's offering prayers to my cheque.
为了你区区十五卢比 还愿却要花掉二十卢比
Prayers for your paltry Rs.15. Cost of offering prayer is Rs.20.
真的吗？太棒了！
lsn't it? Great!
一百五十万？
Rs.15 lakhs?!
谁捐的？
Who donated it?
苏迪普建筑公司的总经理！
Sudeep Constructions MD!
他就捐过一次一百五十万
He gave 15 only once,
但是我每月都捐十五卢比
but l'm giving 15 every month.
天哪…
God...
上帝会祝福那些常常行善之人
God's blessings are always there for good causes.
这是上帝的祝福 把它分给所有的信徒吧
This is God's offering, distribute to all devotees.
别老是这副讨人厌的表情！
Stop that lousy expression!
她把祝福送给每个人 也包括我！
She gave the offering to everyone including me!
她把祝福送给除我之外所有人！
She offered it to all except me!
这意味着我在她心中多么的特别！
lt means how special l'm to her!
仔细想想
Think over it.
走开！
Move!
- 他在说什么？ - 他在感谢您
- What is he saying?  - He's thanking you.
再见 先生！
Bye sir!
你为孩子们做了这么多 我得为你做点什么
You're doing so much for children, l must do something for you.
我已经很久没有像这样享受生活了
lt's been many days since l enjoyed life like this.
第二个放哪儿 纳尼？
Where to place the second, Nani?
- 放那儿！ - 过来看看！
- There!  - Come and show!
你如果事事都要问我 那你来这儿干什么？
lf you ask me everything, what for you're here then?
你过来
You come.
它就在杆子旁边 过来看看！
lt's near the pole, see!
我就没有私人事情吗？
Don't l've any personal work?
坐在这里我有点不舒服
l'm not comfortable here,
先生 我们能坐在那边吗？
sir, can we sit there?
我点的菜是鸳鸯菜
The dish l ordered now is Folio Desate.
在希腊语中是浪漫之餐的意思！
ln Greek it means dish of romance!
这道菜背后有个引人入胜的小故事
There's a colourful flashback behind this dish,
朱利尤斯和克利奥帕特拉共享这份佳肴
Julius Caesar shared this dish with Cleopatra.
所有的情侣都一起分享此道佳肴…
Which ever couple shares this dish together...
我的意思是如果你和我共享的话…
l mean if you and l share it...
你喂我一口
You feed a spoon of it to me.
我喂你一口
l'll feed you a spoon of it to you.
你会因为我的所作所为赢得好声誉
You'll get a good name because of my works.
我想占用点时间和你说点事儿
l wanted to tell you something for quite some time.
你的裙子很漂亮！
Your dress is very nice!
你本人更美 尤其穿着这条裙子
You've added beauty to the dress you wear.
再见！
Bye!
- 再见 先生！ - 好的 快过来
- Bye sir!  - Okay, come.
你最近变瘦了！多吃点哦！
You're growing thin nowadays! Eat well!
菜肴十分美味！
Dish is excellent!
好好照顾他们
You take care of them.
够吗？再见
Enough? Let's meet later.
停下… 停下…
Stop...stop...
麻烦您停下车 先生
Please stop the car, sir.
- 怎么了？ - 我要在这儿下车
- What happened?  - l'll get down here.
这儿？为什么？
Here? Why?
因为… 我想买点儿菜
That is... l want to buy vegetables.
走吧 我陪你去
Let's go, l'll join you.
您应该去股票市场 菜市场不是您该来的地方
Your place is in share market, not is this vegetable market.
先生 您先走吧
You carry on sir.
你的驾照是 红十字会…
You've license, RC...
你戴头盔了吗？
Do you've helmet?
- 今晚都是你值班吗？ - 是的
- Are you on duty till evening?  - Yes l do.
你先替我保管着
Till then guard it.
多少钱？
How much?
她在问你话呢？快点说啊！
lsn't she asking you? Tell her!
十卢比一公斤
Rs.10 a kilo.
十卢比
Rs.10.
十卢比？
Rs.10?
没门儿 先生
No way sir.
不需要 我们从别家店买
No need, we'll buy it from another shop.
喂 嫂子！
Hello sister-in-law!
你怎么这么晚还不回家？
Why are you so late?
这么晚你在办公室干嘛？
What are you doing in office so late?
是晚上十点了吗？
ls it 10 pm?
不是 是晚上七点！
No, 7 pm!
我一忙工作就忘了时间 我这就下班
l didn't observe time in busy work. l'm leaving office right now.
怎么这时候没油了？
Does it have to go empty now?
请告诉我总共要花多少钱
Please tell me how much all this would cost.
我们不需要您的钱 神父 祝福我们就好了
We'll not take money from you, Father, just bless us.
您的祝福法力无边 神父！
Your blessing is very powerful, Father!
- 怎么了？ - 宾都给我发了条短信
- What happened?  - Bindu has sent a message.
这是她对我的首次回应
First time a positive response from her.
是条空白短信！
lt's a blank message!
空白短信就好像空头支票
Blank message is as powerful as blank cheque,
你可以填上任何数字 想象任何内容
You can fill any amount there and imagine anything here.
那么这条空白短信里应该写的是什么？
What could be in the blank message?
速速过来 不要和闲人浪费时间
lt means come immediately without wasting time with wastrels.
你的…信息…
Your...message...
你发了一条空白短信！
You sent a blank message!
我本来想删掉短信来着 结果不小心发错了
lnstead of deleting the message, l sent a reply by mistake.
今天晚上下班有点晚！我有点害怕！
lts late night! l'm scared!
你为什么不公开说出来
Why don't you come out openly
发条短信让我来陪你？
and sent a message to accompany me?
不要多想
Don't imagine too much.
今天晚上下班有点晚！
lts late night!
有点害怕…我是说我有点害怕！
Scared... l mean l'm scared!
我能和你走走吗？
Can l walk with you?
♫ 我有点理解又有点不理解… ♫
♪ l can understand little and a little l can't... ♪
♫ 有时你很得意… ♫
♪ At times you're proud... ♪
♫ 有时你又保守… ♫
♪ At times you're little open... ♪
♫ 有时你责怪我… ♫
♪ At times you may chide me... ♪
♫ 有时你又对我微微笑… ♫
♪ At times you may smile faintly at me... ♪
♫ 在你内心深处… ♫
♪ lnto your deep heart... ♪
♫ 我能用放大镜看看… ♫
♪ May l with magnifying glass... ♪
♫ 看看有没有我的一席之地… ♫
♪ See myself in some corner of it... ♪
♫ 你就不能看我一眼吗？♫
♪ Can't you have a glance at me? ♪
♫ 你就不能和我说句话吗？♫
♪ Can't you have a word with me? ♪
♫ 至少表示一下讨厌我啊… ♫
♪ At least show annoyance on me... ♪
♫ 在你想被称赞时就不能问问我吗？♫
♪ Can't you ask me if you want to get praised? ♪
♫ 我正在为你慢慢发疯 ♫
♪ l'm going mad slowly for you ♪
♫ 你却一点同情心都没有… ♫
♪ but you've no sympathy for me... ♪
♫ 你是个小气的女孩… ♫
♪ You're a miserly girl... ♪
♫ 你为何不和我说话？♫
♪ why don't you talk to me? ♪
♫ 卸掉你内心的防备… ♫
♪ Bring down the fence surrounding you... ♪
♫ 通过微风传递给我信息… ♫
♪ Just send me a message through wind... ♪
♫ 我就会马上来到你身边… ♫
♪ l'll be with you in ajiffy... ♪
♫ 尽管我没有翅膀 ♫
♪ Though l don't have wings ♪
♫ 难道我就不能把你带到星星上去吗？♫
♪ Won't l take you to the stars? ♪
♫ 过想过的生活… ♫
♪ Let it be any life... ♪
♫ 我怎么就不能成为你的生活伴侣？♫
♪ Won't l be your life partner? ♪
♫ 难道你不明白 ♫
♪ Don't you know ♪
♫ 我会因你开心而开心吗？♫
♪ my heart is residing happily in your heart? ♪
♫ 难道你不明白 ♫
♪ Don't you know ♪
♫ 我会因你开心而开心吗？♫
♪ my heart is residing happily in your heart? ♪
你为什么打我？我根本不认识你！
Why are you beating me? l don't know who you are!
拜托放了我吧… 拜托…
Please leave me...please...
任何女人都会为了我变得像疯狗一样
Any woman would follow me madly like a dog,
但是却因为你 我没有得到她
but l didn't get her because of you.
- 你在说谁啊 先生？ - 宾都！
- Who are you talking about, sir?  - Bindu!
离宾都远点！
Stay away from Bindu!
我会杀了你的！
l'll kill you!
你要杀了我？
Will you kill me?
就凭你 也能杀了我？
我的宾都 问你在哪里！
My Bindu is asking where you are!
告诉她 你正在我的脚下垂死挣扎！
Tell her that you're dying at my feet!
给我把他的鞋子和袜子脱掉了
Remove the shoes and socks.
我要慢慢感受你的生命在消逝！
l want to feel your life slip away!
伪装成意外事故
lt must look like an accident.
纳尼 我是宾都！
Nani, its Bindu here!
为什么不回我的短信？
Why don't you talk to me?
你在报复我 让你追求我整整两年的时间吗？
Are you taking revenge on me for making you chase me 2 years?
快点过来找我！
Please come soon!
- 纳尼在家吗？ - 不在
- ls Nani in home?  - No.
要是他回来了 让他打电话给我
Ask him to call me if he comes.
好的
Okay.
- 是你报的警吗？ - 是的 长官
- ls it you who called me?  - Yes sir.
- 什么时候发现的？ - 早上五点！
- When did you see it?  - Morning 5 am!
有人认识他吗？
Does anyone know him?
要是有认识他的人 别害怕 告诉我
Tell me without any fear if you know him.
如果有人知道任何有关他的信息…
lf you give any information about him...
♫ 你是我心中满溢出的爱… ♫
♪ You're the love overflowing from my heart... ♪
♫ 为何你从来都没有看我一眼？♫
♪ Why don't you look at me for once? ♪
♫ 宾都…宾都… ♫
♪ Bindu...Bindu... ♪
♫ 看看我… ♫
♪ look at me... ♪
♫ 不要离开我… ♫
♪ Don't go away from me... ♪
- 为什么起这么早？ - 去办公室
- Why did you get ready so early?  - To office.
办公室十点才开门呢 为什么你七点就要走？
Your office starts at 10 am, why are you leaving at 7 am?
为什么要自己洗呢？
Why are you washing utensils?
我们有付钱请佣人来干活啊
We're paying maid servant to do that.
去 坐下
Go, sit there.
你怎么回事 宾都？
What happened to you, Bindu?
你以前从来不做家务的
You always avoided household work,
但是最近从早干到晚的 一刻也不停下
but now you're working all through the day without rest.
为什么不和我说说呢？
Why don't you talk to me?
出什么事了？
What happened?
我想让自己忙起来 这样就可以不再想念他了
l'm trying to forget by keeping myself busy.
什么？
What?
谁？
Who?
- 纳尼！ - 纳尼？
- Nani!  - Nani?
我戏弄他 假装不在乎他
l teased him by acting as if l don't care about him.
但是我再也见不到他了！
But he has gone far beyond my reach!
他现在肯定在戏弄我！
He's teasing me now!
都说泪水可以清洗心灵
They say crying will ease your heart.
但是我越哭就会越想念他 嫂子
But the more l cry the more l remember him, sister-in-law.
所以我不想再哭了
That's why l don't want to cry.
为了在你最幸福的时候把这个给你…
ln your happiest moment, to give it to you...
这是纳尼给你做的饼干
Nani made these special crackers for you.
再见！
Bye!
你在想念纳尼吗？
Are you missing Nani?
你怎么知道的？
How do you know it?
我的老婆也过世了！
My wife's death!
在她临死前 我坐在她的床边 她让我答应她
On her death bed, holding my hand, she took a promise from me,
等到她死后 让我忘了她
if she dies, l must forget me,
她说如果我忘了她 她会开心的
she said she'll be happy only if l forget her.
如果你真的爱纳尼 就必须忘了他
lf you really love Nani, you must forget him.
您怎么了 先生？
What happened, sir?
没事…
Nothing...
您没事吧？
Any problem?
我…
There l was...
您怎么了 先生？
What happened, sir?
我这么做 只是想让你信任我
l did this to gain your trust.
我以为您有麻烦了
l feared you were in trouble.
- 我吓到你了吗？ - 不是
- Did l scare you?  - Nothing like that.
嗨 苏迪普先生也在呢！
Hey, Sudeep sir is here!
您什么时候来的 先生？
When did you come, sir?
想吃点饼干吗？
Would you like to have biscuit?
他说要去上班了 是吧？
He says he wants go to office, right?
这些傻瓜非得这个时候进来吗？
Do these idiots have to come now?
我会记住您的话的 先生
l'll remember what you said, sir.
我会试着忘了纳尼
l'll try to forget Nani.
半个小时之内禁止打扰我 知道了吗？
No disturbance for 30 minutes, okay?
好的 先生
Okay sir.
把轮子固定住
Put the wedge.
不会再动了
Won't
有人在吗？
ls anyone there?
您怎么到这个位置来的 先生？
Why did you come here, sir?
把我弄出去！
Get me out!
小心点！
Be careful!
动作快点！
Do it fast!
慢点… 慢点…
Slowly...slowly...
没听到我喊人吗？
Didn't you hear me?
您说过禁止打扰的啊 先生
You ordered not to disturb, sir.
您要干嘛 先生？
What are you doing sir?
不 先生！
No sir!
不要 先生 不要打我 先生
No sir, don't beat me sir.
待在那儿别动！
Stay put there!
总经理已经深陷加纳帕蒂的化工厂骗局
MD is fully exposed
而无法脱身
in the Ganapathi Chemical scam.
他马上就要被赶下台了！
He'll be stripped!
先生 不要再追我了
Sir, please leave me.
您说要马上见我 先生
You asked me to meet you urgently, sir.
我上周在德里偶遇教育部长
l met Education Minister in Delhi last week.
如果你们可以和他见面
lf you meet him
顺便再详细说下细节问题
and explain the details,
我们就能拿到国际认证了
we'll get national recognition.
国际水平的？
National level?
我明天要去德里 你们谁和我一起去
l'm going to Delhi tomorrow, if anyone of you join me,
我为你们引荐他
l'll introduce you to him.
我去 先生
l'll come, sir.
演讲可不像吃比萨那么简单
Presentation isn't as easy as eating a pizza.
- 你去吧 宾都  - 我？
- You go with him, Bindu.  - Me?
收藏家们都很欣赏你的演讲才华
Collector too appreciated your presentation.
就是 对啊！
Yes, right!
你在考虑什么呢？你就和他一起去吧
What are you thinking? You go with him.
先生 宾都和你一起去
Sir, Bindu will come with you.
还考虑什么啊？你一定要和他一起去
What are you thinking? You must go with him.
- 去吧！ - 去吧！
- Go!  - Go!
你就去吧！
You go!
我和您去吧
l'll come with you.
我们明天机场见
Let's meet at airport tomorrow.
你他妈的为什么不打扫房间？
What the hell are you doing without cleaning the house?
房间里都是苍蝇！
Room is full of flies!
到处都是苍蝇！
Full of flies!
小子 只有猪才成群地行动呢！
Boy, only pigs come in groups!
狮子都是单独出击！
Lion attacks alone!
单独出击！
Attacks alone!
先生 我是宾都！
Sir, Bindu here!
Sir, its Bindu here!
嗨 宾都！
Yes Bindu!
我现在在机场！
l'm at the airport!
还有三十分钟就要登机了
Just 30 minutes to board the flight.
- 路上塞车！ - 不是吧！
- l'm stuck in a traffic jam!  - Oh no!
你先去安检 我会准时到达的
You take the boarding pass. l'll be there on time.
退回去！
Go back!
干嘛往这里挤？
Why did you shove into this place?
看什么看？
What man?
- 快点！ - 好的 先生
- Make it fast!  - Okay sir.
您好 先生 您怎么在这里 先生？
Greetings sir. How come you're here, sir?
我的车堵在里面出不来了
My car is stuck in traffic jam,
但是我需要马上赶到机场去
need to rush to airport immediately.
用我的车吧 先生 把钥匙给他
Take my car, sir. Give him the keys.
宾都 我还在路上…
Bindu, l'm on the way..
没关系 先生 飞机晚点三十分钟
No problem sir, flight is delayed by 30 minutes.
- 您来得及的  - 我就快到了
- You can reach in time.  - l'll reach.
♫ 苍蝇… 苍蝇… ♫
♪ Fly...fly... ♪
死亡的警钟已经敲响… ♫
♪ death knell to you... ♪
♫ 苍蝇… 苍蝇… ♫
♪ Fly...fly... ♪
我要杀了你
幕间休息
尽管车祸十分严重 你却只受轻伤而已
Though met with a serious accident, you escaped with minor injuries.
把手给我 我给你量下血压
Give me your hand, l'll check your BP.
- 这是什么？ - 防蝇的
- What's this?  - Fly repellant.
给我吧 来
You take it.Give.
不用 给我量血压吧！
Not that, take my BP!
我给你打点镇定剂让你好好睡一觉吧
l'll give sedation to sleep,
给他打两毫升安定
give him Diazepam 2 ml.
我先走了
l'll take leave now.
动物会报复人吗？
Do animals take revenge?
没听到我说话吗？
Didn't you hear me?
动物会报复人吗？
Do animals take revenge?
会的 先生…在电影里面！
They do sir... in Vittalacharya's films!
不是电影里 在现实生活里！
Not in films, but in real life!
现实生活中也会的 先生
lt happens in real life too sir.
我奶奶说的！
My grandma said!
好像是有条眼镜蛇王报复过我爷爷
lt seems a King Cobra took revenge on my grandpa.
不是的 是更小的动物！
Not that smaller ones!
更小的蛇也会报复的
Smaller ones too take revenge.
- 其它的…  - 再小的蛇也报复人的
- Others...  - Smaller snakes too take revenge.
不是蛇！更小的… 像是麻雀啊！
Not snakes! Smaller ones...like sparrow!
青蛙啊！
Frog!
- 苍蝇啊！ - 苍蝇？
- Fly!  - Fly?
会的 先生！
lt will, sir!
要是蛇能的话 为什么苍蝇不能呢？
lf snakes can, why not flies?
白痴！
ldiots!
我应该和谁探讨一下这个问题呢？
With whom should l share this problem?
我还能告诉谁呢？
How am l to tell?
真心无语了
l don't get it.
先生 宾都小姐来看望您了
Sir, Bindu madam is here.
您手里的是什么？
What's in your hand?
有一只苍蝇烦死我了
A fly is irritating me.
♫ 宾都… 宾都… ♫
♪ Bindu...Bindu... ♪
看看我… ♫
♪ look at me... ♪
♫ 不要离开我… ♫
♪ Don't go away from me... ♪
和我说说吧
Tell me.
只是个小小的推测而已
A small doubt.
苍蝇会特别地针对某个人
Do flies target humans
然后施行报复行为吗？
specifically?
我的意思是
l mean
记住某个人然后有计划地施行报复行为
remember humans and attack with a plan.
您是打算写科幻小说吗 先生？
Planning to write science fiction, sir?
这是真事 不是科幻小说
This is a fact not science fiction.
有一只苍蝇不让我吃饭
A fly is not letting me to eat,
不让我睡觉 不让我好好地活着
sleep or live peacefully.
这次的车祸也是它的杰作！
This accident too is its handiwork!
它在玻璃上写着 我要杀了你
lt wrote 'l will kill you' on the windshield.
这是科幻小说吗？
ls it science fiction?
您说自己整晚没有睡觉
You said you didn't sleep all the night.
您的压力太大了
Already you're highly stressed,
然后车祸就自然而然地发生了
accident happened then,
同时一只苍蝇扰乱了您的生活
and a fly too disturbed you at the same time.
因此您就觉得是那只苍蝇的问题
You'd have imagined fly was responsible for it in that stress.
您需要精神病医生的帮助
You need a psychiatrist's help.
你的阳寿还未尽！
You're not yet done with!
过来！
Come!
走开！
Go away!
为什么现在就到我这儿来了呢？
Why would you come to me now?
保险箱和火柴盒！
Safe locker and match box!
当你的脸被煤烟模糊 你就会来到我这儿了
When your face gets smeared by soot, you'll come to me.
你他妈的谁啊？
Who the hell is he?
这是幻觉吗？
ls it imagination?
宾都 来吃饭
Bindu, come for dinner.
怎么了？
What happened?
纳尼送我的吊坠坏了 嫂子
Nani's locket is broken, sister-in-law.
你知道的 纳尼不会回来了
You know Nani will not come back,
你要活在他的回忆里面多久呢？
how long will you live in his memories?
就像这个坏掉的吊坠一样 忘了他吧
Snap your relationship with him like this broken locket.
♫ 我的爱都是属于你的… ♫
♪ My love is all yours... ♪
♫ 但是却只是个梦而已… ♫
♪ lt's just a dream... ♪
♫ 抛开你所有的悲伤… ♫
♪ Leave all your sorrows... ♪
我是纳尼
l'm Nani.
我是纳尼 重生之后的纳尼
l'm Nani, reborn.
你是纳尼？
Are you Nani?
你真的是纳尼？
Are you really Nani?
我不敢相信
l can't believe it.
纳尼复活了？
Nani born again?
你的死是个意外 是吗？
You died in an accident, right?
不是意外？
Wasn't it an accident?
那是？
Then?
苏迪普！
Sudeep!
苏迪普怎么了？
What about Sudeep?
苏迪普… 他杀了你？
Sudeep...did he kill you?
他为什么要杀你？
Why would he kill you?
因为我？
For me?
但是为什么是你？
But why you?
我现在该怎么做？
What should l do now?
怎么做？
How to kill him?
♫ 看 夜幕就要落下… ♫
♪ Look, the night is looming large over... ♪
♫ 死亡正在敲打你的房门… ♫
♪ Death is knocking at your door... ♪
♫ 飞吧… 飞吧… ♫
♪ Fly...fly... ♪
♫ 飞吧… ♫
♪ fly... ♪
♫ 我的名字是纳尼 ♫
♪ My name is Nani ♪
♫ 我也许只是只苍蝇… ♫
♪ l may be just a fly... ♪
♫ 我是一颗核弹 ♫
♪ l'm a nuclear missile ♪
♫ 准备要炸掉你的心… ♫
♪ about to explode in your heart... ♪
♫ 你的射程也许很大 ♫
♪ Your range may be large ♪
♫ 我的体型也许很小… ♫
♪ and my size may be small... ♪
♫ 如果不把你的王国搞垮 ♫
♪ lf l don't bring down your empire ♪
♫ 我就不是男人… ♫
♪ l'm not a man... ♪
♫ 飞吧… 飞吧… ♫
♪ Fly...fly...fly... ♪
♫ 死亡的警钟已经敲响… ♫
♪ death knell to you... ♪
♫ 我会轻易地要了你的命… ♫
♪ l'll take your life easily... ♪
♫ 虽然只是一团小小的火花… ♫
♪ Though it's just a spark... ♪
♫ 难道它就没有力量 ♫
♪ Doesn't it have the power ♪
♫ 烧掉整片森林吗？♫
♪ to burn down a forest? ♪
♫ 虽然只是一颗小小的水滴… ♫
♪ Though it may be just a drop... ♪
♫ 难道它就没有力量 ♫
♪ Doesn't it have the power ♪
♫ 淹没整个地球吗？♫
♪ to drown the earth? ♪
♫ 一只普通的家生苍蝇能奈我何？♫
♪ What can an ordinary house f1ly do to me? ♪
♫ 在你自信地放松以前… ♫
♪ Before you relax with that confidence... ♪
♫ 难道我就不能像生物病毒一样 ♫
♪ Won't l enter your breath ♪
进入你的呼吸道？♫
♪ like bio virus? ♪
着火了 快灭火！
lt's burning, put it off!
♫ 死前有很多事情需要做… ♫
♪ Many a things to be done before the deadline... ♪
♫ 只有十件事情而已！♫
♪ Just ten things! ♪
♫ 第一 杀了你… ♫
♪ One, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第二 杀了你… ♫
♪ two, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第三 杀了你… ♫
♪ Three, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第四 杀了你… ♫
♪ four, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第五 杀了你… ♫
♪ Five, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第六 杀了你… ♫
♪ six, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第七 杀了你… ♫
♪ Seven, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第八 杀了你… ♫
♪ eight, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第九 杀了你… ♫
♪ Nine, to kill you... ♪
♫ 第十 追着你 一定弄死你… ♫
♪ Ten, to hound and pound you to death... ♪
♫ 我要煽动我的翅膀… ♫
♪ l'll shuffle my wings... ♪
♫ 我要在你耳边 ♫
♪ l'll ring the death knell ♪
♫ 鸣起死亡的钟声… ♫
♪ in your ears... ♪
♫ 我要像人体炸弹一样攻击你… ♫
♪ l'll attack you like a suicide bomber... ♪
♫ 用钩子和利爪杀掉你 ♫
♪ By hook or crook l'll kill you ♪
♫ 成为烈士… ♫
♪ and become a martyr... ♪
♫ 对于死过一次的人 ♫
♪ Death is nothing for a man ♪
♫ 死亡并不算什么… ♫
♪ who died once... ♪
♫ 一只普通的家生苍蝇能奈我何？♫
♪ What can an ordinary house fly do to me? ♪
♫ 难道我不能在取了你的性命之后 ♫
♪ Won't l fly away like a rocket ♪
♫ 像火箭一样飞走吗？♫
♪ after taking your life? ♪
这就是你的隐藏之处吗？
ls this your hideout?
抓到了！我抓到它了！
Got it! l got it!
去死… 去死…
Die...die...
去死… 去死吧…
我要一杯卡布奇诺 你呢？
A cappuccino for me, and for you?
你也喜欢卡布奇诺？
You too like cappuccino?
不好意思 小姐！您的咖啡里有一只苍蝇
Sorry, madam! A fly in your coffee.
它在喝咖啡
Fly is having coffee.
下一个节目是什么？
What's the next program?
你预定好防弹玻璃了吗？
Did you order for bullet proof glasses?
是的 先生
l have sir.
不只是苍蝇 没有我的允许
Not just flies,
就算空气都可以进来
even air mustn't enter without our knowledge.
需要我把房子密封起来吗 先生？
You want me to make it airtight, sir?
现在看它还怎么进来！
Let me how will it dare enter now!
请进 先生
Go in sir.
找到了 先生！
Sir, l found it!
看 在他的头发上！
Look, it's in his hair!
还找什么找啊？直接拍死它
What are you searching? Beat it.
为什么打我？
Why are you beating me?
检查他的衣领 在衣领上面
Check his collar. lt's in his collar.
它要逃走了 小心！
lt's escaping, watch out!
请坐
Please sit here.
我顺路过来看看您身体怎么样 先生
Dropped in just to inquire about your health, sir.
雕像真漂亮
Antique statues are very beautiful.
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
这是我的个人收藏
My personal collection.
我的妻子最喜欢在这儿看风景
The place you're standing was my wife's favourite spot.
怎么了 先生？
What happened, sir?
我也很喜欢在这儿看风景
l love your wife's favourite spot.
我们坐下吧 先生？
Shall we sit there, sir?
我突然想起…一件紧急的事情要处理
l forgot something... need to be in urgently.
我想和你一起呆会儿
l wanted to spend some time with you.
晚点儿再离开不行么？
Can't you go little late?
现在…
This time...
我不会耽误您太长时间的 先生
l'll not take much time, sir.
把门打开
Open the door.
♫ 苍蝇…苍蝇…苍蝇…♫
♪ Fly...fly...fly... ♪
♫ 死亡已经敲响你的丧钟… ♫
♪ death knell to you... ♪
♫ 我能轻易置致人于死地… ♫
♪ l'll take your life easily... ♪
♫ 苍蝇 ♫
♪ Fly ♪
这是谁的签名？
What's this signature?
你知道这项目有多么重要吗？
Do you know how big project we're dealing with?
滚！
Get out!
重新复印一份！
Get another copy!
嗨 小贼！你在吗？
Hey thief! Are you here?
我知道你藏在哪儿！快出来！
l know where you are hiding! Come out!
别白费力气了！
Don't try too much!
你的任务成功完成了么？
Did you accomplish the task successfully?
你在和谁说话 宾都？
Who are you talking to Bindu?
我在打电话 嫂子
l'm talking over phone, sister-in-law.
你可真聪明 想藏哪儿就藏哪儿
You're smart, you can hide anywhere you want to.
你可给我惹上麻烦了
l'm getting into trouble because of you.
我能告诉嫂子 我爱你吗？
Can l tell my sister-in-law that you're my lover?
只有这个办法了！
There's only one way out!
你必须变成人！
You must become human!
不用着急
You don't worry,
你总有一天会变的 我对我们的感情有信心
you'll change. l've full faith in our love.
求你了 老兄！一定要保证会议顺利！
l beg you, buddy! Ensure this meeting goes well!
他们要投资两千亿卢比
They're here to invest Rs.2000 crores.
搞砸了的话 我们就要损失两千亿卢比了
lf you mess up, we'll lose Rs.2000 crores,
还要退还他们预付的五百亿卢比
and have to return their advance of Rs.500 crores with interest.
我难道不知道么？
Don't l know this?
看了我们的汇报
l think you'll invest more
相信您一定会增加投资力度的
after seeing our presentation.
不用惊讶！我们都知道他对赛车很感兴趣！
Don't get surprized! We know his passion of racing!
他是在告诉大家
He's symbolically telling you
我们将以这种方式结束这个项目
we'll finish the project like that.
他带了一顶帽子
He has come wearing a helmet.
两千亿卢比！我们到对面去！
2000 crores! We'll go to the streets!
这将成为我国最大的城镇
lt'll be the country's largest township.
如果各位愿意投资
With the investment you've made,
我们将购买五千吨钢材 一万吨水泥
bought 5000 tons of steel, 10000 tons of cement,
和一万五千吨驱蝇剂
and 15000 tons of fly repellant.
驱蝇剂？
Fly repellant?
我是说砖！谁说驱蝇剂了？
Bricks! Who said fly repellant?
难道我会怕苍蝇吗？
Am l scared of flies?
砖 头！
B-R-l-C-K-S!
每个潜在买主
Any prospective buyer
都必须至少先打死一千只苍蝇
must kill at least 1000 flies
才能入住我们的公寓
to get our flat.
如果消灭了所有苍蝇
When all the flies are wiped out,
苏迪普小镇就会从此变得安宁…
Sudeep township will be at peace...
欢乐…安静…和平！
...happy...silent... will be peaceful!
这是什么鬼话？
What's this nonsense?
难道这次董事会和电视节目
ls it board meeting or TV program
要讨论怎么消灭苍蝇和蚊子？
to kill flies and mosquitoes?
驱蝇剂效果不明显！
Repellent is not effective!
我就知道 驱蝇剂根本没什么效果
l know that repellents are not effective on flies.
你…
Hey you...
你怎么了 先生
You don't feel bad sir.
我会自己清理的
l'll clean it myself.
打电话给委员
Get me the Commissioner on line.
听我说 你们可以立刻搜查这里吗？
l'll give you a tip, can you raid immediately?
先生 我们的处境很尴尬
Sir, we're in a soup,
米凯什已经给税收专员打电话了
Mukesh has called lncome Tax Commissioner.
- 他说要搜查我们这里  - 什么？
- He gave him a tip of raiding us.  - What?
所有的钱都在办公室里面
Entire cash is in office.
安全锁和火柴盒！
Safe locker and match box!
如果烟灰弄脏了你的脸 要记得来找我
When your face gets smeared by soot, you'll come to me.
你的话成真了 我现在一无所有了
l lost everything, your words have come true.
你在这里埋下了死亡的种子！
Seed for your death was sown here!
我就是在这儿杀了纳尼！
l killed Nani here!
纳尼…苍蝇…
Nani...fly...
纳尼重生变成了一只苍蝇！
Nani is reborn as fly!
离宾都远点儿！否则 我杀了你！
Stay away from Bindu! l'll kill you!
你说得对 纳尼就是那只苍蝇…
You're right, Nani is the fly...
现在我该怎么办？
What should l do now?
立刻献上祭品！
Conduct a sacrifice immediately!
快看！它被困住了！
Look there! lt's stuck!
做点儿什么啊！
Do something man!
快点念咒语啊！
Chant some hymns!
念咒语啊！把门打开！
Put motifs! Open the door!
咒语也没有办法使门打开啊
There are no hymns to open the shut door.
离宾都远点儿！否则 我杀了你！
Stay away from Bindu! l'll kill you!
我 杀 了你！
l-W-l-L-L-K-l-L-L-Y-O-U!
我要是再晚来一分钟 你就死定了
lf l was a minute late, you'd be dead by now.
这些巫术是怎么回事？
What's this nonsense with witchcraft?
这儿发生什么事了？
What's going on here?
那么 那个死人是谁？
Okay, who is that dead man?
密宗！
Tantra!
他来这儿干什么？
Why did he come here?
消灭那只苍蝇！
To kill the fly!
苍蝇…苍蝇…
Fly...fly...
你为什么这么在意苍蝇？
what's this madness about flies?
你连一只笨苍蝇都怕吗？
Are you scared of a silly fly?
什么笨苍蝇？你知道它有多大能耐吗？
What silly fly? Do you know its capacity?
你去杀了它！你要是个男人
You kill it! lf you're a man,
就去杀了它 我会看着的
kill it, l'll watch it.
杀了它！
Kill it!
你疯了！
You've lost your mind!
我只是实话实说而已
l'm telling you the truth.
那只苍蝇就是纳尼 就是我杀死的那家伙
That fly is Nani, the man l killed.
就是他！他重生变成了苍蝇
lt's him! He's reborn as fly!
它不仅制造了那场车祸 还烧了我们的钱
That fly created that accident and burnt our cash.
为了不让它进来 我把房间布置得严防死守
l made foolproof arrangements to keep it out of home.
我连换气孔都没留
l didn't let even a pinhole open for air also to enter,
但那只苍蝇还是进来了…
but that fly comes in from somewhere...
发生了什么事？
What happened?
这只苍蝇居然带了面具和武器…
A mask and weapons for the fly...
宾都松开了螺丝
Bindu is unscrewing it.
你说得对！
You were right!
那只苍蝇就是纳尼！
Nani is the fly!
老兄 对不起！我刚才还在怀疑你
Sorry buddy! l didn't believe you.
我们现在知道宾都和那只苍蝇是一伙儿的！
We know Bindu is an accomplice of the fly!
干掉他们并不难办
lt's not big deal to finish them off.
我会小心的
l'll take care of it.
但是 我们先得阻止那群准备撤资的家伙们
Before that we must stop the investors
他们会毁了我们的
who are hell bent on ruining us.
如果我们明天还不退钱
lf we don't pay by tomorrow,
他们就要上法庭起诉我们了
they'll go to the court.
先想想这个该怎么办
Think about that first.
要是我们当中有人死了会怎么样？
What if one of our partners dies?
那合同就自动失效了
Contract will get cancelled.
保险公司还会赔付我们七百亿卢比
Moreover we'll get Rs.700 crores from insurance.
你在胡说些什么？你难道会自杀吗？
What are you saying? Will you commit suicide?
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
想跟我玩捉迷藏吗？
Playing games with me?
好吧
Okay.
你怎么这么惊奇？
Why are you so shocked?
我突然过来 吓到你了吗？
Did l surprize you by coming up?
门开着 又没有人 所以我就自己上来了
Door was open downstairs and nobody was there, so l came up.
没关系的 先生
No problem sir.
我有点重要的事情想跟你谈谈
l want to discuss important matter with you.
请跟我走一趟
Please come with me.
我还有工作…
l've work...
跟你说了以后 你该不会觉得我是个疯子吧？
You won't think l'm mad after hearing what l say, right?
有只苍蝇要杀我！
A fly is trying to kill me!
我为什么不相信？
Don't believe it?
我就知道你会相信的
l know you'll believe it.
更令人吃惊的是…
More shocking than that is...
那只苍蝇还有帮凶
Someone is helping that fly to kill me.
你相信吗？
Do you believe it?
如果您这么说的话 我就…
l do if you say so...
如果我告诉别人 他们会说我疯了
When l told this to others, they said l'm mad.
看看这个！
Look at this!
这是监控录像
lt was caught on CCTV camera.
当我把它放大的时候…
When l zoom it...
它居然带了面具和护目镜…看到了吗？
lt has a mask, goggles... did you see?
但是苍蝇应该没办法弄到这些东西的
But a fly can't make it,
不是吗？
right?
一定有人在帮它
Somebody must've made it for the fly.
不要哭 疯狂的小姑娘
Don't cry, mad girl.
我没事的
l'll be fine.
只有微雕艺术家才能做出这么微小的东西
Only micro artists can create such minute articles.
但是谁会想要杀死我呢 宾都？
But who would want me dead, Bindu?
你也是个微雕艺术家
You too are a micro artist.
你知道谁想置我于死地吗？
Do you know who wants me dead?
以前 我动一动手指就能得到任何女人
l used to get any woman l desire at the snap of a finger,
是你逼一个疯狂的男人踩死苍蝇的！
you made a mad man stamping flies!
纳尼！你藏哪儿了？出来！
Hey Nani boy! Where are you hiding? Come out!
我知道你就在这儿！
l know you're here!
你每次都鬼鬼祟祟地溜进来…
Like every time you sneak in stealthily...
直接飞过来 落到我的脚下来！
Come straight and fall at my feet!
不然我就杀了她！
lf not l'll cut her throat!
出来 纳尼！
Come out Nani!
你知道我上次是怎么杀死他的吗？
You don't know how l killed him in his previous birth, right?
把我的鞋脱下来
Take off my shoes.
我要亲眼看着你死掉！
l want to feel your life slip away!
抓住宾都！
Catch Bindu!
你今天死定了！
You're finished today!
不在这里 窗帘后面再找找
Not here, search behind the curtains.
- 剩余的子弹呢？ - 用完了 先生
- Where are the bullets?  - Used everything sir.
- 把她给我带过来！ - 那女的不见了
- Drag her to me!  - Madam is missing.
宾都逃跑了吗？
Did Bindu manage to escape?
没有 先生 门上锁了 保安都在里面
No sir, door is locked, security men are inside.
后门也上锁了 先生
Back door is also locked, sir.
她逃不出去的
There's no way she can escape.
只可能藏在这里面哪里了
She would be hiding somewhere here only.
把她给我找出来！
Find her!
我抓到它了！我抓到它了！
l got him! l got him!
折磨了我二十多天 突然就抓到它了
After torturing me for 20 long days and suddenly getting caught,
她也在这里！
that too here!
真不敢相信！
Do you want me to believe it?
纳尼 你死定了！
Nani, you're finished!
看 它飞得多漂亮！
See, how nicely it is flying!
还没完呢！
lt's not over yet!
拿着！
Hold it!
刺它！
Pierce it!
- 求您放了它吧 先生  - 刺那里！
- Please leave it sir.  - Pierce there!
求您了 先生 放了它吧
l beg you sir, please leave him.
才刚刚开始呢 现在就想让我停下来吗？
Started it just now and you want me to stop it?
你们俩玩儿了我这么多天
You both had played with my life for so many days.
我求你们停下来了吗？
Did l ask you to stop it?
刚才玩到哪里了？
Where did l stop it?
你没刺中 要集中注意力 宾都
You're missing him, concentrate Bindu.
瞄准并且刺中他的心脏！
Aim and pierce it right through his heart!
你觉得我会吗？
Did you think l'll pierce it?
好的！
Okay!
好吧
Okay.
你们俩能交谈吗？
Do you both communicate too?
他在说什么？
What is he saying?
别担心这个无赖！
Don't worry about this rogue!
在我死以前 我会先杀了他
l'll kill him before l die!
我要把他烧成灰！
l'll burn him down to ashes!
你要把我烧成灰？
Will you burn me down?
都要死了还这么傲娇！
Still proud even at the face of death!
我就让你瞧瞧 烧成灰是什么样的！
l'll show you what burning is!
给我一盒火柴！
Get me a match box!
♫ 不论生 亦或死 都只为你… ♫
♪ Life or death is for you only... ♪
♫ 我要挽救我的爱人… ♫
♪ l'm saving my love... ♪
我要烧死你！
lt'll burn you!
离宾都远点！否则 我杀了你！
Stay away from Bindu! l'll kill you!
♫ 苍蝇…苍蝇…苍蝇… ♫
♪ Fly...fly...fly... ♪
♫ 死亡已经敲响你的丧钟 ♫
♪ death knell to you... ♪
我回来了
♫ 我的名字是纳尼 ♫
♪ My name is Nani ♪
♫ 我也许只是只苍蝇… ♫
♪ l may be just a fly... ♪
♫ 你的射程也许很大 ♫
♪ Your range may be large ♪
♫ 我的体型也许很小… ♫
♪ and my size may be small... ♪
♫ 如果不把你的王国搞垮 ♫
♪ lf l don't bring down your empire ♪
♫ 我就不是男人… ♫
♪ l'm not a man... ♪
♫ 飞吧… 飞吧… ♫
♪ Fly...fly... ♪
♫ 飞吧… ♫
♪ fly... ♪
♫ 死亡的警钟已经敲响… ♫
♪ death knell to you... ♪
♫ 我会轻易地要了你的命… ♫
♪ l'll take your life easily... ♪
爸爸 这个故事非常有趣
Story is very fun father
但那个小偷最后怎样了呢？
but what happened to the thief?
那个小偷？宾都说过要他改变的 对吧？
That thief? Bindu said you must change, right?
他确实有所改变！
He changed!
他确实改变不少 你知道他现在在做什么吗？
He changed and know what's he doing now?
好久没在酒吧碰到你了 怎么回事？
l don't see you in bar now a days, why?
你喜欢打桩吗？
Would you like to have a peg?
滚！
Get lost!
你工作挺认真的 想去迪拜吗？
You're a good worker, would you like to go to Dubai?
在那儿 你肯定能赚不少钱
You can make money.
我得到一个机会 想去碰碰运气…
l got an opportunity to test my luck...
希望能够干出一番事业…
Promising to take me to the top...
请给我两张票
Two prayer tickets please.
拿着
Take it.
请问你要干什么？
What do you want please?
最近没见你常来 还好吗？
l don't see you here quite often now, are you fine?
我很好 先生
l'm fine, sir.
你为什么买两张票？
Why did you buy two tickets?
- 因为…  - 有好消息吗？
- That is...  - Any good news?
是的
Yes.
他是谁？
Who is he?
你可能不太能够接受
lt may be unpalatable to you.
揍他…打死这个骗子！
Beat him...beat the crook!
居然敢到教堂里偷东西 你这酒鬼！
How dare you try to steal a temple, you drunkard!
你打我的时候一点慈悲之心都没有
You're getting me beaten mercilessly,
敢跟我赌一瓶威士忌吗？
can you bet me a bottle of whisky?
被打了还死不悔改 把他打到鼻青脸肿
Though beaten up, no remorse, beat him black and blue.
你恋爱了吗？
Didn't you find a human to fall in love?
我说了 你可能不太能够接受
l told you it'll be unpalatable to you.
他要开始一段新的人生！
lt's a new lease of life to him!
你可真善良！
lt's all your goodness!
双手接住它 一切都会好起来的！
Give it with your hands, everything will be fine!